I've got a bottle, where does it go?
It's made of plastic, where does it go?
Let's sort out all the trash!
The plastic goes in the plastic bin.
I've got a box, oh, where does it go?
It's made of cardboard, where does it go?
Let's sort out all the trash!
The cardboard goes in the cardboard bin.
I've got a can, oh, where does it go?
It's made of metal, where does it go?
Let's sort out all the trash!
The metal goes in the metal bin.
I've got a jar, oh, where does it go?
It's made of glass, so where does it go?
Let's sort out all the trash!
The glass things go in the glass bin.
I've got an apple core, where does it go?
It's leftover food, so where does it go?
Let's sort out all the trash!!!
The food scraps go in the compost bin.
Let's sort out all the trash!
Sorting out trash is good for the earth.